const AlgebraQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is the value of x in the equation 2x + 3 = 7?",
        options: ["x = 1", "x = 2", "x = 3"],
        correct_option: "x = 2"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the solution to the equation x^2 - 4 = 0?",
        options: ["x = 2 or x = -2", "x = 4 or x = -4", "x = 1 or x = -1"],
        correct_option: "x = 2 or x = -2"
    },
    {
        question: "Simplify the expression: 3(x + 2) - 4x.",
        options: ["-x + 6", "3x + 2", "-x - 6"],
        correct_option: "-x + 6"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the value of y in the equation y/3 + 2 = 5?",
        options: ["y = 3", "y = 9", "y = 15"],
        correct_option: "y = 9"
    },
    {
        question: "Solve for x: 5x - 3 = 2x + 6.",
        options: ["x = 1", "x = 3", "x = 2"],
        correct_option: "x = 3"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the product of (x + 3)(x - 3)?",
        options: ["x^2 - 9", "x^2 + 9", "x^2 - 6"],
        correct_option: "x^2 - 9"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the value of the expression 2x when x = 5?",
        options: ["10", "7", "5"],
        correct_option: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "Simplify the expression: 4x - 2x + 7.",
        options: ["2x + 7", "2x - 7", "6x + 7"],
        correct_option: "2x + 7"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the value of x if 3x = 12?",
        options: ["x = 4", "x = 3", "x = 6"],
        correct_option: "x = 4"
    },
    {
        question: "If y = 3x + 2, what is the value of y when x = 4?",
        options: ["y = 14", "y = 12", "y = 10"],
        correct_option: "y = 14"
    }
];

export default AlgebraQuestions;
